<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP site Wout Wynen</title>
    <link>http://wout-wynen.github.io/categories/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP site Wout Wynen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 13:51:01 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://wout-wynen.github.io/categories/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of a software tool in the training company: Van Roey Automation</title>
      <link>http://wout-wynen.github.io/Review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 13:51:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wout-wynen.github.io/Review/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;n-able-software-review-solarwinds-company:34ebcfd1cfa3321b387d6c584f68cba4&#34;&gt;N-able software review (solarwinds company)&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.forbesimg.com/media/lists/companies/solarwinds_416x416.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image of SolarwindsLogo&#34; /&gt;

&lt;br&gt;
The N-able software is from the company Solarwinds and is one of the global leaders in IT management software and IT service providers.
&lt;br&gt;
It is specialized in providing a lot of information about the devices connected in a network.
&lt;br&gt;
Many companies use it to ease the communication between departments and help out the customers as quickly as possible.
&lt;br&gt;
With the advanced techniques it is also able to notify the users when a technical difficulty is happening with any of the devices.
&lt;br&gt;
Van Roey uses this program with basically everything. When they arive and put the computer on, the program is already running. They use every feature of the software: communication, service, reports, etc..
&lt;br&gt;
The N-able software is in my opinion great software to use in big companies.
&lt;br&gt;
It is easy to use and it has a lot of monitoring tools.
&lt;br&gt;
I’m not a fan of the monitoring tools, because they are a bit sketchy and hard to understand.
&lt;br&gt;
I think they need to make fewer tools and put more effort into them individually.
&lt;br&gt;
The notification that the staff gets on their phones and computers is a very useful feature.
&lt;br&gt;
There is still one downside to the notifications though:
&lt;br&gt;
When you have installed the app on your phone, there is no way for you to turn the notifications offline without uninstalling the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I don’t know the company personally but based on previous reviews and the opinions of a couple of users, there are not many updates within the company.
&lt;br&gt;
This means that there are sometimes flaws and bugs in the system.
&lt;br&gt;
I’ve heard that the company have been running pretty flat for more than 5 years now and that doesn’t surprise me. I haven’t heard of this company even once and if I hadn’t done my internship with a company that uses this software, I would probably never have heard of it.
&lt;br&gt;
Although they are one of the global leaders in IT management software, I still think that there is a lot of room for improvement when it comes to publicity and updates.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The N-able software is great in general, but it has its flaws.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
I don’t know the price of the software. There is no information about it on the site and I can’t seem to find an estimation anywhere. However, If it is not too expensive, I’d definitely recommend it but right now it does not earn my vote.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MY LIFE AND IT</title>
      <link>http://wout-wynen.github.io/Autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 13:51:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wout-wynen.github.io/Autobiography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I am Wout Wynen, a 17-year old student in the 6th year at the Immaculata High school in Oostmalle and I’m going to tell you a little bit more about my life in IT so far. What I have accomplished, what I want to accomplish ,what I love about IT management and so on.
&lt;br&gt;
My first experience with IT was back when I was just a little boy of about 6 years old. My parents bought their first computer and I was astonished about what it was and how it worked. At first I didn’t know how the concept of internet worked but after spending many hours learning, I finally managed to play my first game. I found it to be so much fun that I spent some days after school just playing the game and discovering new things. I still don’t really know how I managed to play it without any help but I’m kind of proud of it now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I was into computers at such a young age, I’ve been interested in computers ever since I discovered them. IT means a lot to me now but in a totally different way than before.
I like the different aspects of computer programming and hardware more than ever before. The gaming aspect has become less interesting for me over the past year because I simply prefer discovering and learning new things for example: how to build a site. I spend a lot of my free time on the internet but not in an addictive way. I spend mostly about two hours on a regular day but that’s schoolwork included. Sometimes I feel like doing some programming but on other days I just prefer to play games with friends. I would not consider myself an expert but maybe in the future that title will come my way.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to do something with IT for a living. I’m not really sure what field of IT I am more interested in. Hardware and software are both very interesting fields for me but I think after this year, I will have my answer. At the moment I like the software part a bit more but that might just be for a short period of time because last year I was more into hardware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life would be totally different without IT. I have no idea what I would be doing then, and I don’t want to think about it anyway. I like the way my life is right now and I am doing what I love doing the most. When you study IT, it’s of course a major part in your life but not in a bad way. You can talk with friends even after school, play games with them, and just have fun in general.&lt;br /&gt;
I hope I will find a job in IT someday because then I never have to work a day of my life.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://scontent-ams2-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xpt1/t31.0-8/12138391_914998781870469_5782153303557822632_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image of Wout Wynen&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>